Prints and Printing Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
Prints and Printing Slide Collection
1960-2005
VRC 1400
Yale University Arts Library
12
68 boxes in 12 containers
Collection consists of color and black and white 35 mm slides of printing techniques and prints worldwide.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
Collection consists of color and black and white 35 mm slides of printing techniques and prints worldwide.
Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically by geographical region or country. Further arranged by individual artist name. Individual artist name sections may be preceded by either or both an anonymous or miscellaneous grouping. Preliminary section on printing techniques (lettering and printed books).
Prints; Printing; Slides; Reproductions
- Austria (Box 1)
  - Anonymous & Miscellaneous Artists [Slide box 1] (Box 1)
  - Hoffmann, Josef, 1870-1956 (Box 1)
  - Klimt, Gustav, 1862 1918 (Box 1)
  - Kokoschka, Oscar, 1886-1980 (Box 1)
  - Kubin, Alfred, 1873-1959 (Box 1)
  - Loeffler, Berthold, 1874-1960 (Box 1)
  - Moser, Kolo, 1868-1918 (Box 1)
  - Mucha, Alphonse Marie, 1860-1939 (Box 1)
  - Schiele, Egon, 1890-1918 (Box 1)
- Belgium (Box 1)
  - Broodthaers, Marcel, 1924-1976 (Box 1)
  - Ensor, James, 1860-1949 (Box 1)
  - Kerkhoven, Leonard van de, c.1828-1898 (Box 1)
  - Stroobant, P., act.c.1854 (Box 1)
  - Velde, Hanry van de, 1863-1957 (Box 1)
- Britain (Box 1)
  - 16th Century (Box 1)
  - 17th Century (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous Artists (Box 1)
    - Milton: Paradise Lost (Box 1)
      General
      See also: for Illustration –Prints France—Cheron, Louis
  - 18th Century [Slide box 2] (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous Artists & Titles (Box 1)
    - William Hunter: Anatomy of the Human Gravid Uterus (Box 1)
    - Pope, A.: Rape of the Lock (Box 1)
  - 19th Century (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous Artists & Titles (Box 1)
  - Various Artists (Box 1)
    - Boydell Shakespeare Prints (Box 1)
    - Allan, David, 1744-1496 (Box 1)
    - Armitage, Edward, 1817-1896 (Box 1)
    - Barry, James, 1741-1806 [Slide boxes 2-3] (Box 1)
    - Bateman, H.M,. Act.c.1910 (Box 1)
    - Bauner, Lewis, act.c.1908- [Slide box 3] (Box 1)
    - Beardsley, Aubrey, 1872-1898 (Box 1)
    - Beckett, Isaac, 1653-1719 (Box 1)
    - Beggarstaff (Nicholson, Pryde) (Box 1)
    - Bell, John, 1763-1820 (Box 1)
    - Bell Vanessa, 1879-1961 (Box 1)
    - Bewick, Thomas, 1753-1828 (Box 1)
    - Bickham, George II, -d.1758 (Box 1)
    - Blake, William, 1757-1827 (Box 1)
      - Miscellaneous Titles [Slide box 3-4] (Box 1)
      - Albion Rose (Glad Day) [Slide box 4] (Box 1)
      - America (Box 1)
      - Canterbury Pilgrims (Box 1)
        - Gates of Paradise (Box 1)
      - Europe (Box 1)
      - God Creating… (Ancient of Days) (Box 1)
      - House of Death (Lazar House) (Box 1)
      - Jerusalem (Box 1)
      - Book of Job [Slide boxes 4-5] (Box 1)
      - Marriage of Heaving & Hell [Slide box 5] (Box 1)
      - Book of Thel (Box 1)
      - Songs of Experience (Box 1)
      - Songs of Innocence (Box 1)
      - Book of Urizen [Slide boxes 5-6] (Box 1)
      - Visions of the Daughters of Albion [Slide box 6] (Box 1)
    - Bonington, Richard, 1801-1828 (Box 1)
    - Bouvier, Joseph, ac.1839-1888 (Box 1)
    - Boys, Thomas S., 1803-1874 (Box 1)
    - Brown, Grafton Tyler, 1841-1918 (Box 1)
    - Browne, H.K. ("Phiz") (Box 1)
    - Bunbury, Henry-W., 1770-1811 (Box 1)
    - Calvert, Edward, 1799-1883 (Box 1)
    - Catherwood, Frederick, 1799-1854 [Slide boxes 6-7] (Box 1–2)
    - Caulfield, Patrick [Slide box 7] (Box 2)
    - Clough, Prunella, 1919- (Box 2)
    - Cohen, Harold, 1928- (Box 2)
    - Constable, John, 1776-1837 (Box 2)
    - Cope, Charles West, 1811-1890 (Box 2)
    - Cox, David, 1783-1859 (Box 2)
    - Cozens, Alexander, c.1710-1786 (Box 2)
    - Crane, Walter, 1845-1915 (Box 2)
    - Crane, Walter, 1845-1915 (Box 2)
    - Cruikshank, Isaac, 1756-1811 (Box 2)
    - Dampier, William, 1651-1715 (Box 2)
    - Daniell, Thomas, 1749-1840 (Box 2)
    - Daniell, William, 1769-1837 (Box 2)
    - Dodd, Daniel (Box 2)
    - D'Oyly, Charles, 1781-1845 (Box 2)
    - Dresser, Christopher, 1834-1904 (Box 2)
    - Du Maurier, George, 1834-1896 [Slide boxes 7-8] (Box 2)
      Also known as Du Maurier, George Louis Palmella Busson
    - Dyce, William, 1806-1864 [Slide box 8] (Box 2)
    - Earlom, Richard, 1743-1822 (Box 2)
    - Egerton, Daniel T., ac.1824-1842 (Box 2)
    - Eistrack, Renold, 1571-c.1625 (Box 2)
    - Evans, Merlyn, 1910-1973 (Box 2)
    - Fairland, Thomas, 1804-1852 (Box 2)
    - Flaxman, John, 1755-1826 (Box 2)
      See also, Painting Britain—Flaxman
    - Forrest, Charles Ramus, act.c.1802-1827 (Box 2)
    - Fraser, James Baillie, 1783-1856 (Box 2)
    - Frith, William Powell, 1819-1909 (Box 2)
    - Fuseli, Henry, 1741-1825 (Box 2)
    - Gainsborough, Thomas, 1727-1788 (Box 2)
    - Gillray, James, 1757-1815 [Slide boxes 8-9] (Box 2)
    - Girtin, Thomas, 1775-1802 [Slide box 9] (Box 2)
    - Green, Charles, 1840-1898 (Box 2)
    - Gribelin, Simon, 1661-1733 (Box 2)
      For frontispiece to Shaftbury's "Judgment of Hercules" after Paolo de Matteis, see Painting U.S--.West, Benjamin, Comp.
    - Griggs, F.L., 1876- (Box 2)
    - Gwynne-Jones, Allan, 1892-1982 (Box 2)
    - Haden, Francis S., 1818-1910 (Box 2)
    - Hamilton, Richard, 1922- (Box 2)
    - Harris, Claudius, 1828-1882 (Box 2)
    - Harvey, William, 1796-1866 (Box 2)
    - Hayman, Francis, 1708-1776 (Box 2)
    - Hayter, Stanley W., 1901- (Box 2)
    - Heath, William, 1795-1840 (Box 2)
    - Hermes, Gertrude, 1901- (Box 2)
    - Hockney, David, 1937- (Box 2)
    - Hodges, William, 1744-1797 (Box 2)
    - Hodgkin, Howard, 1932- (Box 2)
    - Hogarth, William, 1697-1764 (Box 2)
      - Various Titles [Slide boxes 9-10] (Box 2)
      - Analysis of Beauty [Slide box 10] (Box 2)
      - Beer Street and Gin Lane (Box 2)
      - Boys Peeping at Nature (Box 2)
      - Cockpit (Box 2)
      - Credulity, Superstition & Fanaticism (Box 2)
      - The Election (Box 2)
      - The Enraged Musician (Box 2)
      - Four Stages of Cruelty (Box 2)
      - Four Times of Day (Box 2)
      - A Harlot's Progress [Slide boxes 10-11] (Box 2)
      - Industry and Idleness, 1747 [Slide box 11] (Box 2)
      - Illustration to Milton's Paradise Lost (Box 2)
      - March of the Guards (Box 2)
      - Marriage a la Mode (Box 2)
      - Peregrination in Kent (Box 2)
      - The Rake's Progress (Box 2)
    - Houghton, Arthur Boyd, 1836-1875 (Box 2)
    - Hudson Thomas (after) (Box 2)
    - Hull, Frank, 1845-1888 (Box 2)
    - Image, Selwyn, 1849-1930 (Box 2)
    - Jeffreys, James, 1751-1784 (Box 2)
    - Kauffer, Edward Mcknight, 1890-1954 (Box 2)
    - Kidd, J.B. (Box 2)
    - Kitaj, Ronald B., 1932- (Box 2)
    - Knapton, George, 1698-1778 (Box 2)
    - Kneller, Sir Godfrey (after) (Box 2)
    - Kohler, George F. (Box 2)
    - Kowalski, Elaine, 1948- (Box 2)
    - Lawless, Matthew J., 1837-1864 (Box 2)
    - Lear, Edward, 1812-1888 (Box 2)
    - Leech, John, 1817-1864 [Slide box 12] (Box 2)
    - Lely, Sir Peter (after) (Box 2)
    - Lens, Bernard, 1659-1725 (Box 2)
    - Maclise, Daniel, 1806-1870 (Box 2)
    - Mackmurdo, Arthur, 1851-1942 (Box 2)
    - Martin, John, 1789-1854 (Box 2)
    - Millais, Sir John E., 1829-1896 (Box 2)
    - Morland, George (after) (Box 2)
    - Morris, William, 1834-1896 (Box 2)
    - Morrow, Albert George, 1863-1927 (Box 2)
    - Mortimer, John, 1741-1779 (Box 2)
    - Nicholson, William, Sir, 1872-1949 (Box 2)
    - Northcote, Thomas (Box 2)
    - Ottley, William Young, 1771-1826 (Box 2)
    - Palmer, Samuel, 1805-1881 (Box 2)
    - Paolozzi, Eduardo, 1924- [Slide box 13] (Box 3)
    - Pasmore, Victor, 1908- (Box 3)
    - Passe, Wm. Van de, c.1598-1637 (Box 3)
    - Phillips, George, act.1839- (Box 3)
    - Pinwell, George J., 1842-1875 (Box 3)
    - Prout, Samuel, 1783-1852 (Box 3)
    - Pugin, A. Welby (Box 3)
    - Rackham, Arthur, 1867-1939 (Box 3)
    - Reynolds, Joshua (after) (Box 3)
    - Richards, Ceri, 1905- (Box 3)
    - Richmond, George, 1809-1896 (Box 3)
    - Roberts, Wm. Patrick, 1895-1980 (Box 3)
    - Rollinson, William, 1762-1842 (Box 3)
    - Rossetti, Dante Gabriel, 1828-1882 (Box 3)
    - Rowlandson, Thomas, 1756-1827 (Box 3)
    - Runciman, Alexander, 1736-1785 (Box 3)
    - Salt, Henry, 1780-1827 (Box 3)
    - Sambourne, E. Linley, 1844-1910 (Box 3)
    - Sandby, Paul, 1725-1809 (Box 3)
    - Sandys, A.F.A., 1829-1904 (Box 3)
    - Scarfe, Gerald, 1936- (Box 3)
    - Sharp, William, 1749-1824 (Box 3)
    - Schetky, John Christian, 1778-1874 (Box 3)
    - Short, Frank, 1857-1934 (Box 3)
    - Simons, I.P. (Box 3)
    - Stadler, Joseph C., ac.1780-1812 (Box 3)
    - Stafford, John Phillips, 1851-1899 (Box 3)
    - Stothard, Thomas, 1755-1834 (Box 3)
    - Stubbs, George, 1724-1806 (Box 3)
    - Sutherland, Graham, 1903-1980 (Box 3)
    - Talbert, Bruce James, 1838-1881 (Box 3)
    - Tenniel, John, 1820-1914 (Box 3)
    - Thackeray, Wm. M., 1811-1863 (Box 3)
    - Thew, Robert, 1758-1802 (Box 3)
    - Thomassin, Henry Simon, 1687-1741 [Slide box 14] (Box 3)
    - Thomson, John, 1817-1921 (Box 3)
    - Tilson, Joe, 1928- (Box 3)
    - Townsend, Henry James, 1810-1890 (Box 3)
    - Trotter, Thomas, c.1750-1803 (Box 3)
    - Turberville, George, act.c.1570-c.1600 (Box 3)
    - Turner, Joseph Mallord William, 1775-1851 (Box 3)
    - Vandergucht, Gerard, 1696-1776 (Box 3)
    - Wadsworth, Edward Alexander, 1889-1949 (Box 3)
    - Walker, Frederick, 1840-1875 (Box 3)
    - Walker, John, 1939- (Box 3)
    - Walton, W.I. (Box 3)
    - Ward, James, 1769-1859 (Box 3)
    - Watts, George Frederick, 1817-1904 (Box 3)
    - Webber, John (after), 1751-1793 (Box 3)
    - Westall, Richard, 1765-1836 (Box 3)
    - Wheatley, Francis (after) (Box 3)
    - Wilson, Richard, 1714-1782 (Box 3)
    - Wootton, John, c.1682-1765 (Box 3)
- Flanders (Box 3)
  Approximate dates: Flanders –until 1830 Belgium/Holland –after 1830
  - 15th Century (Box 3)
  - 16th Century (Box 3)
    - Various Titles (Box 3)
    - Nadal, Evangelicae Historiae Imagenes (Box 3)
    - Master of the Small Landscapes (after) (Box 3)
    - Borcht, P. van der, ac.1552-1608 [Slide box 15] (Box 3)
    - Brueghel, Pieter, Elder, 1525-1569 (Box 3)
    - Bry, Theodore de, 1528-1598 (Box 3)
    - Cock, Hieronymus, 1510-1570 (Box 3)
    - Coecke van Alst, Peter I, 1502-1550 (Box 3)
    - De Bruyn, Nicholas, c.1570-c.1635 (Box 3)
    - Diepenbeeck, A., 1596-1675 (Box 3)
    - Galle, Phillip, 1537-1612 (Box 3)
    - Galle, Theodor, 1571-1633 (Box 3)
    - Hogenberg, Franz, ac.1540-c.1590 (Box 3)
    - Liere, Joose van (after) (Box 3)
    - Lipsius, Justus, 1547-1606 (Box 3)
    - Massys, Cornelis, 1511-1580 (Box 3)
    - Rubens, Peter Paul, 1577-1640 (Box 3)
      - Various Titles (Box 3)
      - Pompa Introitus Ferdinandi, 1642 (Box 3)
        For Pompa Introitus sketches see Painting Flanders –Rubens, Antwerp, and Leningrad
    - Sadeler, Aegidius, 1570-1629 (Box 3)
    - Sadeler, Jan, 1550-1600 (Box 3)
    - Schorknes, Hans, 1618-1630 [Slide box 16] (Box 3)
    - Van Dyck, Anthony, 1599-1641 (Box 3)
    - Vellert, Dirk J., ac.1511-1544 (Box 3)
    - Vesalius, Andreas, 1514-(?)1564 (Box 3)
    - Vorsterman, Lucas, 1595-1675 (Box 3)
      For Prints Flandres L. Vorsterman, see also Prints Flanders –Rubens, P.P
    - Wierix, Jan, 1549-1615 (Box 3)
    - Zutman, Lambert, 1510-1567 (Box 3)
- France (Box 3)
  - 14th Century (Box 3)
  - 15th Century (Box 3)
  - 16th Century (Box 3)
  - 17th Century (Box 3)
  - 18th Century (Box 3)
    For Events of the French Revolution see also Painting France 18th century
    - Various Titles [Slide boxes 16-17] (Box 3)
    - Diderot, Denis –Encyclopedie... (Box 3)
      For portrait of Diderot see Painting France –Loo, L.M. van
    - Voltaire Apotheosis (Box 3)
  - 19th Century (Box 3)
    - Various Titles [Slide boxes 17-18] (Box 3)
    - Ballet Scenes [Slide box 18] (Box 3)
    - Historical Events (Box 3)
    - Illustrations for Chateaubriand, Genie du Christianisme (Box 3)
    - Illustrations from Dupont, Chansons (Box 3)
    - Illustrations from Texier, Tableau de Paris 1853 (Box 3)
  - 20th Century (Box 3)
    For Prints 20th c see also Commercial Art Posters
    - Various Titles [Slide box 19] (Box 4)
    - Minotaure (Box 4)
    - Apollinaire, Guillaume, 1880-1918 (Box 4)
    - Arnoux, Charles, 1820-1883 (Box 4)
      See also Painting France –Manet-- Cartoons
    - Arp, Jean (Hans), 1887-1966 (Box 4)
    - Audouin, Pierre, 1768-1822 (Box 4)
    - Baudouin, P.A., 1723-1769 (Box 4)
    - Beatrizet, Nicolas, 1515-c.1565 (Box 4)
    - Bellange, Hippolyte, 1800-1866 (Box 4)
    - Bellange, Jacques, ac.1602-1617 (Box 4)
    - Besnard, Albert, 1849- 1934 (Box 4)
    - Bonnard, Pierre, 1867-1947 (Box 4)
    - Bosse, Abraham, 1602-1676 (Box 4)
    - Boucher, Francois, 1703-1676 [Slide boxes 19-20] (Box 4)
    - Bouchardon, Edme, 1678-1762 [Slide box 20] (Box 4)
    - Boudin, Eugene, 1824-1898 (Box 4)
    - Boulanger, Louis, 1806-1867 (Box 4)
    - Boyvin, Rene, c.1525-c.1580 (Box 4)
    - Bracquemond, Felix, 1883-1914 (Box 4)
    - Braque, Georges, 1882-1962 (Box 4)
    - Bresdin, Rudolphe, 1822-1885 (Box 4)
    - Buhot, Felix Hilaire, 1847-1898 (Box 4)
    - Callot, Jacques, 1592-1635 (Box 4)
      - Various Titles (Box 4)
      - Miseries & Misfortunes of War (Box 4)
    - Cassandre, A.M., 1901-1968 (Box 4)
    - Cezanne, Paul, 1839-1906 (Box 4)
    - Challemel, J. (Box 4)
    - Chardin, J.B.S., 1699-1779 (Box 4)
    - Chauveau, Francois, 1613-1676 (Box 4)
    - Cheret, Jules, 1836-1932 (Box 4)
    - Cheron, Louis, 1655-1713 [Slide box 21] (Box 4)
    - Claude, Gallee, 1600-1682 (Box 4)
    - Cochin, C.N., the younger, 1715-1790 (Box 4)
    - Cocteau, Jean, 1889-1963 (Box 4)
    - Colibert, Nicholas, 1750-1806 (Box 4)
    - Colin, Paul, 1892-1985 (Box 4)
    - Corot, Jean B.C., 1796-1875 (Box 4)
    - Courbet, Gustave, 1819-1877 (Box 4)
    - Cross, Henri E., 1856-1916 (Box 4)
    - Daubigny, Charles, 1817-1878 (Box 4)
    - Daumier, Honore, 1808-1879 (Box 4)
      - Various Titles (Box 4)
      - From "Le Charivari" (Box 4)
      - Bathers from "Le Charivari" [Slide boxes 21-22] (Box 4)
    - David, J.L., 1748-1825 [Slide box 22] (Box 4)
    - Debucourt, Philibert L., 1755-1832 (Box 4)
    - Degas, Edgar, 1834-1917 (Box 4)
      - Various Titles (Box 4)
      - After the Bath (Box 4)
      - Au Louvre (Mary Cassatt) (Box 4)
      - Portraits (Box 4)
    - Delacroix, Eugene, 1798-1863 (Box 4)
    - Delaune, Etienne, 1519-1583 [Slide box 23] (Box 4)
    - Denis, Maurice, 1870-1943 (Box 4)
    - Desenne, A.J., 1785-1827 (Box 4)
    - Deveria, Achille, 1800-1857 (Box 4)
    - Dore, Gustave, 1832-1883 (Box 4)
      For a photograph of Dore, see Photograph France
    - Drevet, Pierre, 1663-1783 (Box 4)
    - Dubuffet, Jean, 1901- (Box 4)
    - Duchamp, Marcel, 1887-1968 (Box 4)
    - Duche de Vancy, Gaspar, c.1768-1788 (Box 4)
    - Dupre, Jules, 1811-1889 (Box 4)
    - Duvet, Jean, c.1485-1561 (Box 4)
    - Eisen, Charles, 1720-177 (Box 4)
    - Erte, 1892- (Box 4)
    - Fantin-La Tour, H., 1836-1904 (Box 4)
    - Faivre, Jules Abel, 1867-1945 (Box 4)
    - Fautrier, Jean, 1898-1964 (Box 4)
    - Focillon, Victor, 1849-1918 (Box 4)
    - Forain, J.L., 1852-1931 (Box 4)
    - Fragonard, J.H., 1732-1806 [Slide box 24] (Box 4)
    - Galice, Louis (Box 4)
    - Ganiere, Jean, d.c.1698 (Box 4)
    - Garnier, Jules, 1847-1889 (Box 4)
    - Gauguin, Paul, 1843-1903 (Box 4)
      - Various Titles (Box 4)
      - Joys of Brittany (Box 4)
      - Noa, Noa (Box 4)
    - Gavarni, Paul, 1804-1866 (Box 4)
    - Gerard, Francois Pascal Simon, 1770-1837 (Box 4)
    - Gericault, Theodore, 1791-1837 (Box 4)
    - Gerome, Jean-Leon, 1824-1904 (Box 4)
    - Gill, Andre (Box 4)
    - Gillot, Claude, 1673-1722 (Box 4)
    - Girodet-Trioson, A.L., 1767-1824 (Box 4)
    - Godefroy (Box 4)
    - Gourmont, Jean I, c.1483-1557 (Box 4)
    - Grandville (J.I.I.Gerard), 1803-1847 (Box 4)
    - Grasset, Eugene, 1845-1917 [Slide box 25] (Box 5)
    - Gravelot, Hubert Francois, 1699-1773 (Box 5)
    - Gross, Antoine J., 1771-1835 (Box 5)
    - Huet, Paul, 1803-1869 (Box 5)
    - Ibels, Henri, 1867- (Box 5)
    - Ingres, J.A.D., 1780-1867 (Box 5)
    - Janinet, Jean-F., 1752-1814 (Box 5)
    - Jollat, Mercure, act.c.1545- (Box 5)
    - Juste, Juste de, 1505-1559 (Box 5)
    - Lafitau, Joseph-Francois (Box 5)
    - La Hyre, L., 1606-1656 (after) (Box 5)
    - Lancret, N., 1690-1745 (Box 5)
    - LeGeay, Jean Lauren (Box 5)
    - Leger, Fernand, 1881-1955 (Box 5)
    - Legros, Alphonse, 1837-1911 (Box 5)
    - Lejeune, Louis F., 1775-1848 (Box 5)
    - LePautre, Jean, 1617-1682 (Box 5)
    - Le Prince, J.B., 1734-1781 (Box 5)
    - Mallarme, Stephane, 1842-1898 (Box 5)
    - Manet, Edouard, 1832-1883 [Slide boxes 25-26] (Box 5)
    - Marlet, J.H., 1771-1847 [Slide box 26] (Box 5)
    - Marot, Daniel, 1655-1718 (Box 5)
    - Martinet, Pierre (Box 5)
    - Masson, Andre, 1896- (Box 5)
    - Matisse, Henri, 1869-1954 (Box 5)
    - Mellan, Claude, 1598-1688 (Box 5)
    - Meryon, Charles, 1821-1868 (Box 5)
      - Various Titles (Box 5)
      - Notre Dame (Box 5)
      - Pont-Au-Change (Box 5)
    - Millan, Pierre (Box 5)
    - Millet, Jena F., 1814-1875 (Box 5)
    - Monnet, Charles, 1732-1808 (Box 5)
    - Monnet, Charles, 1732-1808 (Box 5)
    - Morisot, Berthe, 1841-1895 (Box 5)
    - Nadar, Tournachon, 1820-1910 (Box 5)
    - Nanteuil, Robert, 1623/30-1678 (Box 5)
    - Onzefant, Amedee, 1886- [Slide box 27] (Box 5)
    - Parrocel, Charles, 1688-1752 (Box 5)
    - Pequegnot, Auguste, 1819-1878 (Box 5)
    - Perrier, Francois, 1590-1650 (Box 5)
    - Phillipon, Charles, 1806-1862 (Box 5)
    - Philippon, Adam, b.1606- (Box 5)
    - Picart, Bernard, 1673-1733 (Box 5)
    - Pissarro, Camille, 1830-1903 (Box 5)
    - Prieur, Jean Louis, 1759-1795 (Box 5)
    - Provost, Alex, ac.1850-1886 (Box 5)
    - Pullon, Jean (Box 5)
    - Ranson, Paul, 1862-1909 (Box 5)
    - Ravenet, S.F. (Box 5)
    - Redon, Odilon, 1840-1916 (Box 5)
      - Various Titles [Slide boxes 27-28] (Box 5)
      - Dans la Reve [Slide box 28] (Box 5)
      - Origins (Box 5)
      - Temptation of Saint Anthony (Box 5)
    - Renoir, Pierre A., 1841-1919 (Box 5)
    - Renouard, Antoine- Agustin (Box 5)
    - Reverdy, Georges, ac.1531-1560 (Box 5)
    - Rochegrosse, George, 1858-1938 (Box 5)
    - Roualt, Georges, 1871-1958 (Box 5)
      - Various titles (Box 5)
      - Miserie (Box 5)
    - Roussel, K.X., 1867- (Box 5)
    - Ruotte, Louis, c.1754-1814 (Box 5)
    - Saint-Aubin, all brothers (Box 5)
    - Salomon, Bernard, c.1506-c.1561 (Box 5)
    - Saly, Jacques, 1717-1776 (Box 5)
    - Signac, Paul, 1863-1935 (Box 5)
    - Steinlen, Alex, 1859-1923 (Box 5)
    - Tissot, James, 1836-1902 (Box 5)
    - Toulouse-Lautrec, Henri, 1864-1901 [Slide boxes 28-29] (Box 5)
    - Vignon, Claude, 1593-1670 [Slide box 29] (Box 5)
    - Verite, J.B. (Box 5)
    - Villon, Jacques, 1875-1963 (Box 5)
    - Vlaminck, Maurice, 1876-1958 (Box 5)
    - Vouet, Simon, 1590-1649 (Box 5)
    - Vuillard, Jean Eduardo, 1868-1940 (Box 5)
    - Watelet, Claude-Henri, 1718-1786 (Box 5)
    - Watteau, Jean-A (after), 1684-1721 (Box 5)
      For prints after Watteau see –Prints France –Cochin, C.N. the younger
- Germany (Box 5)
  - 15th Century (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous Titles [Slide boxes 29-30] (Box 5)
    - Cologne Bible [Slide box 30] (Box 5)
    - Master B.M., ac.1480-1500 (Box 5)
    - Master b x g, ac.1466-1490 (Box 5)
    - Master E.S., ac.1440-1468 (Box 5)
    - Master of 1446 (Box 5)
    - Master of the Garden of Love, ac.1440-1450 (Box 5)
    - Master of the Hausbuch [Slide boxes 30-31] (Box 5–6)
    - Master I A M of Zwolle [Slide box 31] (Box 6)
    - Master I.E. (Box 6)
    - Master of the Nurenberg Passion (Box 6)
    - Master of the Playing Cards (Box 6)
    - Master of S. Erasmus (Box 6)
    - Master W (Box 6)
    - Master of the Weibermacht (Box 6)
- 16th Century (Box 6)
  - Various Titles (Box 6)
  - Reformation Prints (Box 6)
  - Civitates Orbis Terrarum Atlas (Box 6)
  - Luther Bible (Box 6)
  - Master C.R. (Box 6)
  - Master H.L., ac.1510-1533 (Box 6)
- 17th Century [Slide box 32] (Box 6)
  - Various Titles (Box 6)
- 18th Century (Box 6)
  - Various Titles (Box 6)
- 19th – 20th Centuries (Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous Titles (Box 6)
  - Aldegrever, H., 1502-1558 (Box 6)
  - Altdorfer, A.lbrecht, c.1480-1538 (Box 6)
  - Amman, Jost, 1539-1591 (Box 6)
  - Baldung-Grien, Hans, 1480-1545 (Box 6)
    For Comparison –Misc. Perspective—Photograph of foreshortened football player
  - Barlach, Ernst, 1870-1938 (Box 6)
  - Baselitz, George, 1938- (Box 6)
  - Beckmann, Max, 1894-1950 (Box 6)
  - Bayer, Herbert, 1900-1985 [Slide box 33] (Box 6)
  - Beham, Barthel, 1502-1540 (Box 6)
  - Block, Rene, 1942 (Box 6)
  - Brehmer, Klaus Peter, 1938- (Box 6)
  - Burgkmair, Hans, 1473-1531 (Box 6)
  - Campendonk, H., 1889-1921 (Box 6)
  - Campendonk, H., 1889-1921 (Box 6)
  - Cranach, Lucas (elder), 1472-1553 [Slide boxes 33-34] (Box 6)
  - Cranach, Lucas (younger), 1515-1586 [Slide box 34] (Box 6)
  - DeRetza, Franciscus (Box 6)
  - Dexel, Walter (Box 6)
  - Dieterlin, Wendel, c.1550-1599 (Box 6)
  - Dietrich, Christian, 1712-1774 (Box 6)
  - Dix, Otto, 1891-1969 (Box 6)
  - Durer, Albrecht, 1471-1528 (Box 6)
    - World Map (Box 6)
    - Allegory (Box 6)
      - Knight, Death, and the Devil (Box 6)
      - Melancholia (Box 6)
      - Nemesis (The Great Fortune) (Box 6)
    - Animals (Box 6)
    - Book Illustration (Box 6)
      - Various titles (Box 6)
      - Narrenschiff (Box 6)
      - Ritter vom Turn (Box 6)
    - Designs (Box 6)
      - Various Titles (Box 6)
      - Triumphal Arch [Slide boxes 34-35] (Box 6)
    - Mythological [Slide box 35] (Box 6)
    - Portraits (Box 6)
    - Religions (Box 6)
      - Various Titles (Box 6)
      - Adam & Eve (Box 6)
      - Albertina Passion (Box 6)
      - Apocalypse (Box 6)
      - Engraved Passion [Slide boxes 35-36] (Box 6)
      - Large Passion [Slide box 36] (Box 6)
      - Life of the Virgin (Box 6)
      - Little Passion (Box 6)
      - Saints [Slide boxes 37-38] (Box 6–7)
        - S. Jerome (Box 7)
      - Virgin & Holy Families (Box 7)
    - Secular (Box 7)
    - Theory & Measurement (Box 7)
  - Eckmann, Otto, 1865-1902 [Slide box 38] (Box 7)
  - Elsheimer, Adam, 1578-1610 (Box 7)
  - Ernst, Max, 1891-1976 (Box 7)
    For Collages made from prints –Painting Germany
    - Miscellaneous titles (Box 7)
    - Les Malheurs des Immortel, 1922 (Box 7)
    - La Femme 100 Tetes, 1929 (Box 7)
    - Little Girl Dreams…, 1939 (Box 7)
  - Felixmuller, Conrad, 1897-1977 (Box 7)
  - Flotner, Peter, 1491-1546 (Box 7)
  - Friedrich, Caspar D., 1774-1840 (Box 7)
  - Fust and Schoeffer, 15th century (Box 7)
  - Gerung, Matthias, c.1500-c.1570 (Box 7)
  - Graf, Urs, c.1485-c.1527 (Box 7)
  - Grez, Jochen (Box 7)
  - Grieshaber, Hap, 1901-1961 (Box 7)
  - Grimm, Ludwig Emil, 1790-1863 (Box 7)
  - Grosz, George, 1893-1959 (Box 7)
  - Heartfield, John, 1891- (Box 7)
  - Heckel, Erich, 1883-1949 (Box 7)
  - Hirschvogel, A., 1503-1553 (Box 7)
  - Hoch, Hannah, 1889- (Box 7)
  - Hodicke, Karl Horst, 1938- (Box 7)
  - Hofer, Karl, 1878-1955 (Box 7)
  - Holbein, Hans (younger), 1497-1543 (Box 7)
  - Holl, Lienhart, ac.c.1480 (Box 7)
  - Hollar, Wenzel, 1607-1677 [Slide boxes 38-39] (Box 7)
  - Hopper, Daniel (elder), 1470-1536 [Slide box 39] (Box 7)
  - Hopper, Hieronymus, 1520-1550 (Box 7)
  - Huber, Wolf, 1490-1553 (Box 7)
  - Itten, Johannes (Box 7)
  - Jansen, Franz M., 1885-1953 (Box 7)
  - Killian, Lucas, 1579-1637 (Box 7)
  - Kircher, Athanasius, 1602-1680 (Box 7)
  - Kirchner, Ernst Ludwig, 1880-1936 (Box 7)
  - Klinger, Max, 1857-1920 (Box 7)
  - Kolbe, Carl Wilhem, 1781-1853 (Box 7)
  - Kollwitz, Kathe, 1867-1945 (Box 7)
  - Lautensack, Hans, 1524-1561/6 (Box 7)
  - Leblon, Jakob C., 1667-1741 (Box 7)